* [CPD  
    MEMBERSHIP](https://veema.co.uk/leadership-membership/)
* [KEYNOTE  
    SPEAKERS](https://veema.co.uk/conferences-keynotes/)
* [NEWS  
    & MEDIA](https://veema.co.uk/news-media/)

No products in the basket.

No products in the basket.

* [CPD  
    MEMBERSHIP](https://veema.co.uk/leadership-membership/)
* [KEYNOTE  
    SPEAKERS](https://veema.co.uk/conferences-keynotes/)
* [NEWS  
    & MEDIA](https://veema.co.uk/news-media/)

No products in the basket.

* [CPD  
    MEMBERSHIP](https://veema.co.uk/leadership-membership/)
* [KEYNOTE  
    SPEAKERS](https://veema.co.uk/conferences-keynotes/)
* [NEWS  
    & MEDIA](https://veema.co.uk/news-media/)

* [CPD  
    MEMBERSHIP](https://veema.co.uk/leadership-membership/)
* [KEYNOTE  
    SPEAKERS](https://veema.co.uk/conferences-keynotes/)
* [NEWS  
    & MEDIA](https://veema.co.uk/news-media/)

Login
-----

Username or email address \*Required 

Password \*Required 

 Remember me  Log in

Register
--------

Email address \*Required 

A link to set a new password will be sent to your email address.

Your personal data will be used to support your experience throughout this website, to manage access to your account, and for other purposes described in our [privacy policy](https://veema.co.uk/veema-limited-privacy-policy/).

 Register

Veema Limited Privacy Policy
============================

[Home](https://veema.co.uk/) / Veema Limited Privacy Policy

Veema Limited is committed to ensuring your privacy and data are protected and respected. Any future changes we make to our Privacy Policy you will always find on this page.

About the information you provide
---------------------------------

You provide us with information when you:

* Fill in a form on our websites
* Communicate with us by phone, email or social media
* Register for our newsletters and CPD webinars
* Enquire about our services
* Sign up for our events

Personal data may include your name, address, email, phone number or specific information required to deliver a specific service or for attendance at an event.

About the information we collect
--------------------------------

To provide you with a more personalised online experience, our websites automatically collect information about your visit and the services you use there.This information is never shared with other organisations or used for purposes other than intended.

When you visits our websites we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our websites.

We may also collect information about you from publicly available sources.

Security
--------

We use security measures designed to prevent unauthorised access to your data as well as the unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction or damage to it.

Your personal data is stored either with online providers or as part of our secure manual record-keeping system. Online providers we use to store information is Mailchimp (for mailing service) and Google (for any other purpose). Neither providers or their employees have access to the private information we are storing.

Your GDPR rights
----------------

Under GDPR, you have the right to:

* **Be informed** about the collection and use of your data, as outlined in this policy.
* **Access any personal data** we may hold about you.
* **Rectify any inaccurate or incomplete data** we may hold about you.
* **Have your personal data erased.**
* **Restrict processing** of your personal data or limit how it is used.
* **Data portability**, so you can obtain your personal data and reuse it elsewhere.
* **Object to us processing** your personal data under certain circumstances.
* **For us to not make solely automated decisions**, including profiling, that may have a significant impact on you.

You can exercise any of these rights by sending a Subject Access Request to [info@veema.co.uk](mailto:info@veema.co.uk). We will respond in line with current data protection law.

Third-party websites
--------------------

Our website may contain links to third-party websites and content over which we have no control. This privacy statement doesn’t cover those sites and we cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of your data if you visit them. You should read the privacy statement of any third party website you visit and exercise caution when there.

### Links

### Contact Details

Email: [info@veema.co.uk](mailto:info@veema.co.uk)  

**Address:** 20 Emerson Building  
Chadwell Lane  
London  
N8 7RF

**Phone:** [+44 (0) 20 3637 4232](tel:+442036374232)

### Latest Tweets

[What a fab start to my half-term break. TY to everyone who continues to support my work, @VeemaEdu,](https://twitter.com/costa_veemaedu/status/1850886398460510699)[...](#) my leadership journey and of course the team at @routledgebooks. The book is full of practical ideas, research, & my own stories from schools I work with. More to follow soon…

[🙌We are busy planning our next gathering for Junior School Leaders #SoHJuniorSchoolLeadersConf](https://twitter.com/societyofheads/status/1850859625433764301) [...](#)🎉  
  
All of our Junior School Leaders will be welcome at this exciting event full of networking, professional development and collegiality. Book here today! 👀🖱️  
https://www.thesocietyofheads.org.uk/booking

© Copyright 2022 by Veema Limited. Company Registration No. 07799937. All Rights Reserved.

By using cookies on this site, we can personalise the content and social media we show you. It also helps us improve the way the site works by understanding better how visitors use it. If you stay on this site, you will be agreeing to our [Cookie](https://veema.co.uk/cookies-policy) and [Privacy Policies](https://veema.co.uk/privacy-policy), as well as our [Terms and Conditions](https://veema.co.uk/terms-of-use). Accept All

Manage consent

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. These cookies ensure basic functionalities and security features of the website, anonymously.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-analytics | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Analytics". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-functional | 11 months | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Functional". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookies is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Necessary". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-others | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Other. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-performance | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Performance". |
| viewed\_cookie\_policy | 11 months | The cookie is set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin and is used to store whether or not user has consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data. |

Functional

 Functional

Functional cookies help to perform certain functionalities like sharing the content of the website on social media platforms, collect feedbacks, and other third-party features.

Performance

 Performance

Performance cookies are used to understand and analyze the key performance indexes of the website which helps in delivering a better user experience for the visitors.

Analytics

 Analytics

Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.

Advertisement

 Advertisement

Advertisement cookies are used to provide visitors with relevant ads and marketing campaigns. These cookies track visitors across websites and collect information to provide customized ads.

Others

 Others

Other uncategorized cookies are those that are being analyzed and have not been classified into a category as yet.

SAVE & ACCEPT

Download Blog

Direct School Email: \*  

By downloading our blog you agree to our terms and conditions and the information you have provided. We will not share your data for third party use.

×

Download Brochure

First Name: \*  

Last Name: \*  

Direct School Email: \*  

Organisation/School:

Position:

By downloading our membership brochure you agree to our terms and conditions and the information you have provided. We will not share your data for third party use.

×

Newsletter Subscription

First Name: \*  

Last Name: \*  

Direct School Email: \*  

Organisation/School:

Position:

By subscribing to our newsletter, you submit the information you have provided to us. We will use it to communicate with you regarding news, events or other services we feel you would like to hear about. We will never give away your data.

×

Request our service factsheets

First Name: \*  

Last Name: \*  

Direct School Email: \*  

Organisation/School:

Position:

Teacher CPDs:

Asking… Not Telling!On Best BehaviourAssessment in PracticeTeaching for Mastery through Practical DifferentiationWinning at DifferentiationBe Inspection ReadyYour Next Great PlaySafeguarding School PackageWhole-school Safeguarding and Child ProtectionSafer RecruitmentLeading SafelyGovernance LeadershipNational Professional Qualification for Headship (NPQH)National Professional Qualification for Senior Leadership (NPQSL)National Professional Qualification for Middle Leaders (NPQML)Leading the ChargeLeading On Pastoral Care

×

Follow our newsfeed

First Name: \*  

Last Name: \*  

Direct School Email: \*  

Organisation/School:

Position:

By following our newsfeed, you submit the information you have provided to us. We will use it to communicate with you regarding news, events or other services we feel you would like to hear about. We will never give away your data.

×
